# Hugo Puhlmann

## Curriculum Vitae

#### Skills

Advanced Experiencied with C++, C#, version control software (especially git), and Unity3D.

Intermediate Experience with Python and Java for desktop application development. Good mathematical skills, mostly in the field of linear algebra, calculus and analytical geometry.

Basic Understanding of game engine architecture, computer graphics and OpenGL.

Languages Native portuguese speaker. Fluent verbal and written english.

### Experience

2010–2012 **Researcher**, *Grupo de Sistemas de Computação Móvel (GMob), UFSM*, Santa Maria.

Member of a mobile computing research group, developed a few prototype applications for Android and J2ME devices.

2012–2013 **Game Programmer**, *Decadium Studios/IMGNATION Studios*, Santa Maria. Worked using Unity and C# to develop two games, *NBB Game* (Aquiris Studios, Sports) and *Dodge This!* (IMGNATION Studios, Action). Responsibilities included mainly UI programming and general gameplay coding.

2013–2014 IT Analyst/Programmer, Santa Maria Design House (SMDH), Santa Maria.

2014-Present **Software Development & IT** - **Team Leader**, Santa Maria Design House (SMDH), Santa Maria.

2009—Present **Misc. Projects**, https://github.com/hstefan. Mostly utilities and experiments.

#### Education and Awards

2009–2013 Bachelor of Computer Science, Universidade Federal de Santa Maria, UFSM.

2011 ACM ICPC Competition, ACM-ICPC.

40th place in the 2011 Brazilian finals